nextnetmedia.com 2016-06-20

# Privacy and Refund Policy | NextNetMedia.com

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register for an account on nextnetmedia.com.

When registering on our website, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Like most websites, we use cookies and/or web beacons to enhance your experience, gather general visitor information, and track visits to our website. Please refer to the ‘do we use cookies?’ section below for information about cookies and how we use them.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

To personalize your experience  
Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.  
To improve customer service  
Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.  
To send periodic emails  
The email address you provided during registration may be used to send updates pertaining to your account as well as occasional newsletters. You may opt out of the newsletters at any time by using the link at the bottom email.

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information.

Whenever payments are made online, sensitive information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. Payments to BackLinks.com are made through PayPal or 2Checkout.com and both companies provide SSL encryption.

Your personal data is encrypted into our Database to be only accessed by those authorized with special access rights to our systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes, Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Your Consent**

By using nextnetmedia.com, you consent to our web site privacy policy.

**Refund Policy**

If you are not 100% satisfied with your purchase, within 120 days from the purchase date, we will fully refund the cost of your order.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

Next Net Media, LLC

http://www.backlinks.com

316 California Ave. #804  
Reno, NV 89509  
USA  
info@nextnetmedia.com  
1-800-737-5820
